Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/jacki-vu (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Business Strategy
Typography
Build Strong Relationships

Jacki Vu (Nguyên)

Senior Product Designer | UI UX Designer | Product design lead | Open to AI job

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Summary

!' (). 8

:

: 7 years specializing in UI/UX design and product design.

&: 2 years of experience leading and mentoring design teams.

: Always serious and meticulous, with a strong focus on usercentered design.

& : Proven and effective, highly regarded by startups, clients, and users.

':

Collaborating with startups, small to mid-sized businesses and freelance projects to create impressive and effective UI/UX designs. Sharing my knowledge and experience in the field of design. Supporting and mentoring junior designers to develop their skills.

Experience

BEX Realty
Senior UI/UX designer
December 2021 - Present (3 years 4 months)
United States

Arobid.com
Product Design Lead
March 2023 - February 2024 (1 year)
Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Athlema
Product Designer
May 2022 - December 2023 (1 year 8 months)
United States

FPT Software

User Experience Designer

May 2022 - June 2023 (1 year 2 months)

Ho Chi Minh City, Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Fika

Senior UI/UX designer at Fika - Asia's female-focused AI social & dating app

February 2021 - January 2022 (1 year)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Improve the design of the application and establish a strong brand identity, making the application friendly to users. Together with teams dedicated to businesses successfully raising \$ 1.6 million during the Covid-19 pandemic.

GraphicsZoo

Senior User Interface Designer August 2020 - August 2021 (1 year 1 month)

United States

ezequote

UI/UX Design & Senior Architectural Designer May 2018 - June 2020 (2 years 2 months) Vietnam

Dellos F&B Co.,Ltd.
Graphic Designer

May 2017 - May 2018 (1 year 1 month)

Vietnam

Education

The Interaction Design Foundation

Certificate, Design · (January 2022)

Dalat University

Bachelor's degree, Postharvest technology (2012 - 2016)

Arena multimedia

Certificate, Graphic Design · (May 2015 - May 2016)